rabb.it 2014-04-25

# Rabbit

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Rabbit, Inc. and it subsidiaries and affiliated entities (together, “Company”, “we” or “us”) with respect to the collection, use, disclosure and protection of personal and other information about you received or generated by Company when you use or interact with the applications, services and websites offered or made available by us at www.rabb.it, or through corresponding sites on social media outlets (such as through Company’s Facebook page) or through corresponding applications on mobile devices (collectively, the “Site”), including Rabbit’s video chat service for video chatting and content sharing in small or large groups (in both public and private rooms), the associated software application downloaded and installed in order to use such video chat service (including any modifications, updates or versions thereof, the “Rabbit Application”), and any related applications, forums, services, products and information of Company (collectively, together with the Site, the "Services"). By using or accessing the Site, the Rabbit Application or other Services (or when you use Facebook to connect to any Services), or by submitting information to Company, you consent to this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy may be updated or modified from time to time. We will provide notice of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your use of the Services or Site after such update or modification constitutes your acceptance of such changes to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy and you are also subject to the Company’s Terms of Service and User License (the “TOS”) and the applicable terms and conditions of the TOS (including limitations on damages, jurisdiction of disputes and application of law) shall apply to this Privacy Policy and any disputes relating to privacy of information issues hereunder. 

As used in this policy, the terms "using" and "processing" information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally. 

### What Information Do We Collect?

We collect, receive, generate and store the following types of information: 

  * _Personal Information:_ Personal Information is information that can be used to identify or contact you, including but not limited to your name, address, email address, gender, birthday, telephone number, account identifiers, account password, payment information, credit card information and other billing data. We collect, receive and store your Personal Information when you connect or register for the Services (including the Rabbit Application) through Facebook or another third party source (as described below) or when you directly provide such information in connection with sign-up, registration or interaction with Company on or through the Services, including without limitation when you download the Rabbit Application or open any related account or membership, when you subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, or complete your profile through the Services. 

Certain contact and other Personal Information may be necessary to use, sign up or register for Services, utilize certain features or functionality on the Services, or otherwise transact business with us. You can choose not to provide such information, but then you might not be able to use or take advantage of our Services, Site, business transactions or portions thereof. 

  * _Information From Third Parties:_ We collect Personal Information and other information about or related to you from Facebook and potentially other third parties (“Facebook Information”) when you connect, register or sign-up for the Services (including when you download the Rabbit Application). In such cases, you allow Company to access and obtain Personal Information and other Facebook Information about you from Facebook (including from your Facebook profile information and pictures and information about your friends and likes) and such other third parties. The Facebook Information you allow Rabbit to access and collect is affected by the privacy settings you establish with Facebook or such other third parties (and you can control and find out more about these settings by visiting Facebook.com). The Facebook Information is subject to certain terms and conditions which restrict and proscribe our use, disclosure and protection of your Facebook Information in accordance with the applicable policies on Facebook.com (or the websites of such other third parties, if applicable) (the “Facebook Restrictions”). 
  * _User Content:_ User Content is information, data, text, files, software, graphics, music, audio, photographs, video, messages, communications or other materials, that you upload, submit, post, transmit, share or otherwise provide on, through or to the Services. For example, we receive and store User Content you provide to Company when you: 
    1. use the Services; and/or
    2. post, upload, submit or otherwise provide content, materials or other information on, through or to the Services; and/or
    3. fill out surveys or questionnaires or sign up for or enter promotions, events or other special activities on, through or to the Services; and/or
    4. communicate with Company or with other users or participants of the Services (including the content of such communications and information provided in connection with such communications); and/or
    5. provide information to third parties and their web sites, applications and services which are accessed or used by Company or on, through or to the Services.
  * _Information We Collect or Generate About You and/or Your Use of Services:_ We receive, collect, generate and store certain types of information whenever you use the Services or otherwise interact with us. For example, we may automatically record your activity on the Services (such as rooms visited, amount, timing and type of video chatting and sharing activity, content shared, other Users interacted with, etc.), the time and date of your activities, your IP address, browser type, Internet Service Provider, page views, domains, operating system and similar information. Also, we may automatically send and receive information to and from your computer in connection with your use of the Services. Like many websites and online services, we may also use "cookies" (see below), log files, web beacon technologies and other automated tools to obtain certain types of information when your web browser or application (such as your installed Rabbit Application) accesses our Services. 

### How Is Your Information Used?

Company may use the information submitted, collected, received or generated from and/or about you for any of the following purposes (except that Facebook Information is subject to the Facebook Restrictions): 

  * To operate, provide, administer, develop, and improve our Services (including without limitation the Rabbit Application), and to operate and support Company’s related businesses.
  * To better understand how users access and use our Services on an aggregated and individualized basis, to track and monitor usage, to conduct quality control, to fix technical and other errors or problems, to conduct market research and to respond to user desires and preferences.
  * To analyze, compile, publish, sell and otherwise exploit information relating to usage and users of the Services.
  * For advertising, marketing and promotional purposes.
  * To provide personalized experiences and recommendations, language and location customization, personalized help and instructions, or other responses to your usage of our Services.
  * To track memberships, purchases and usage as necessary for the purpose of our complying with any third party agreements or obligations (such as, for example, making royalty or other payments to third parties).
  * To provide you with support and handle inquiries.
  * To communicate with or contact you concerning your account or membership or your usage of or participation in the Services, and for other customer service, This will include use of your e-mail address to send you messages and notices for the purposes described above and below.
  * To bill you, process payments and for authorization, account history and billing purposes. This may include credit card authorization and verification for purchases made from Company, location verification for products and services which may have limited geographical access, and the like.
  * To offer you content, services, or other products and services, including to develop new services and products.
  * To provide you with news and newsletters, special offers, promotions, and targeted advertising.
  * To comply with applicable laws, rules and regulations and any regulatory mandate or court order.
  * To enforce our TOS and other applicable agreements, rights and remedies.
  * To protect the safety of any person, to address fraud, security or technical issues, or to protect Company’s rights or property.

### When is Information Shared with or Disclosed to Others or the Public?

Information provided by our users is an important part of our business. Company will share and disclose information submitted, collected, received or generated from and/or about you only as compatible with the purposes described above, when we have your consent (as may be provided by you from time to time through the Services or otherwise), and as described in this section as follows (except that Facebook Information is subject to the Facebook Restrictions): 

  * _Public Forum:_ Any User Content or other user information, content or materials submitted, posted, shared, transmitted or otherwise provided to public portions of the Services (such as video chat rooms, discussion groups, bulletin boards and similar forums) or portions of the Services designed for broad user access (such as reviews, focused user groups, etc…) are or may be shared with the public without restriction. Company also reserves the right to publish or make publicly available any information that is already publicly available prior to the time first provided to or collected by Company or information that becomes publicly available without any action or omission on the part of Company.\ 
  * _Aggregated Data and Anonymous Data:_ Company may publish and otherwise disclose (a) on an aggregated basis, information regarding usage and users of the Services, and (b) information that is not connected to your name or similar information that would allow you to be specifically identified.• Disclosures In Connection with Permitted Uses. Company may disclose your information to third parties in connection with the purposes described in the previous section such as, for example, to implement advertising, marketing or promotional activities or transactions or to publish, sell and otherwise exploit information relating to usage and users of the Services. 
  * _Company Affiliates:_ We may share your information with our subsidiaries and other affiliates, but only if those entities are either subject to this Privacy Policy or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy. 
  * _Contractors, Collaborators and Agents:_ We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions or otherwise act on our behalf. Examples include processing payments, resolving service problems, correcting errors related to the execution of the Services, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance (including data concerning marketing and promotional programs), hosting websites or software, developing websites and software, providing customer service, assisting Company with providing, administering, developing or improving the Services, and/or for other purposes within the ordinary course of business. These third parties have access to the Personal Information and other information needed to perform their functions on our behalf. We use reasonable efforts to require these companies to (1) provide adequate protections for your Personal Information that are no less protective than those set out in this Privacy Policy and (2) use your Personal Information only for the purposes for which the third party has been engaged by us. We are not liable for the acts or omissions of these third parties, except as provided by applicable law. 
  * _Business Transfers and Collaborations:_ As we continue to develop our business, we might sell the Company and/or its business or assets and/or sell or buy online sites, services, subsidiaries, or other businesses; or we might collaborate or partner with other companies in strategic transactions, business arrangements or licenses. In such transactions, customer and user information and information regarding usage of the Services generally would be one of the transferred business assets or otherwise one of the components of, or involved in, the transaction, we may therefore share this information in connection with such transactions or arrangements. 
  * _Compliance with Law and Protection of Company and Others:_ We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information and any other information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, judicial proceeding, court order, subpoena or other legal process; detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, emergency situations or technical issues; enforce or apply our TOS and other agreements, rights and remedies; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our employees and contractors, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction purposes. 

The Services may include or interoperate with applications, services, features or functionalities provided by third parties. In connection with such third party applications, services, features or functionalities, you may send (or such third parties may get access to) certain information about or related to you or your activities therewith. The use, storage and disclosure of such information by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies. 

### Changing or Deleting Your Information

Company does not have a mechanism for you to review, edit or delete any of your information on or stored in the Services or otherwise by Company. If in the future, the Company may implement a personal profile section of the Services which may allow you to review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in your registration or user profile, but Company has no obligation to provide or create such a section. 

If you would like us to delete your Personal Information in our system, please contact us and we will consider making good faith efforts to accommodate your request, though we have no obligation to do so (and will not do so if we have any legal obligation to retain the record or legitimate business need to retain such information). See below for privacy contact information. In such cases, we ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests because of the reasons stated above or because such requests are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, relate to information that is incorporated into other databases or Services as permitted by this Privacy Policy, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes or derivative information that is not separable), or for other reasons. Because of the way we maintain certain Services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems. 

If some or all of your information is deleted from your Facebook profile or (in the even one is created, in the Company’s user registration or profile section) your account may become deactivated, your right to use the Services may terminate and you may no longer be able to use the Services. We are not responsible for updating, correcting or removing any of your information disclosed to or held by third parties. 

### Cookies and Other Files

Like many services, websites or applications, we may use "cookies" or similar technologies to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's memory for record-keeping purposes. We may use cookies or such other technologies to improve the quality of the Services, including for storing user preferences and tracking user trends and for any of the other purposes permitted in this Privacy Policy. We may utilize persistent cookies to save your registration/member ID and login password for future logins to the Services. We may utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Services, to better understand how you interact with the Services and to monitor aggregate usage by Company users and web traffic routing on the Services. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are usually deleted from your computer when you log off from the Services and then close your browser. Third party advertisers on the Services may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions or functionalities of the Services. 

Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you use the Services, our servers may record certain information that your web browser or the Rabbit Application sends whenever you visit any website or utilize any other services or applications. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other information. When you use the Services, we may employ clear GIFs (also known as web beacons) or similar mechanisms which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. 

### Security and Protection of Your Information

Company is very concerned with safeguarding your information and protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use appropriate, industry-typical security measures and technology to protect against unauthorized access to, or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of, user information covered by this Privacy Policy (excluding any such data that may be disclosed or publicly shared in accordance with this Privacy Policy). In this regard, we employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure and to safeguard your information against loss, theft, alteration and destruction. No method of security is 100% secure. 

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored "personal data" (as defined in applicable statutes on security breach notification) to your via email or conspicuous posting on or through the Services in an expedient manner and without unreasonable delay, insofar as these are consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. 

### International Transfer

Our Services are hosted in the United States. If you use the Services from the European Union, Asia or any other country outside the United States with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use and disclosure that differ from the United States laws and regulations, please be advised that through your continued use of the Services, you are transferring your information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us or use the Services, Company transfers personal information to the United States and processes it there, and your submission of such information represents your consent and agreement to that transfer. 

### Our Policy Toward Children

In order to use our Services you must represent and warrant that you are over the age of 13 in the sign-up process. Children under the age of 13 are not eligible to use the Services and must not attempt to register with the Company and/or submit any personal information to us. We do not knowingly collect personal information from any person who is under the age of 13 or allow them to register. If it comes to our attention that we have collected personal data from a person under the age of 13, we will delete this information as quickly as possible. 

### Links to Other Sites, Services and Applications

Our Services contain links to, interoperate with, and allow you to share content to and from third party services, websites and applications. The fact that we link to a website, service or application or allow you to share content through these third parties is not an endorsement, authorization or representation that we are affiliated with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. Other websites, services and applications follow different rules regarding the collection, use, storage or disclosure of the personal and other information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites, services and applications you use. 

### Limitation of Liability

Even though Company has taken reasonable commercial steps and efforts to prevent your Personal Information and other information covered by this Privacy Policy from being accessed, used, intercepted or disclosed by unauthorized individuals in violation of this Privacy Policy, you should know and you acknowledge that Company cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with your information. You expressly acknowledge and agree that uploading, posting, providing, storing, using, analyzing, transmitting, sharing and/or allowing access to your Personal Information and other information on, through, in or to the Services, and the use of all such Services, are all done at your sole risk and responsibility. You expressly acknowledge that Company is not liable for (i) any special, indirect, consequential, incidental or punitive damages, costs, or liabilities whatsoever arising out of or resulting from your use of the Services, including from your uploading, posting, providing, storing, using, analyzing, transmitting, sharing and/or allowing access to your Personal Information and other information; or (ii) any loss, disclosure or use of your Personal Information or other information. 

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@rabb.it](mailto:info@rabb.it) or write to us at: 

Rabbit Inc.  
625 Second St., 2nd Floor  
San Francisco, CA 94107
